Saranghae.
Saranghae... too.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES]
- Just kidding!
- [MUSIC STOPS]
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
What does that mean?
It means "joke."
It's just a joke.
So this is just a joke?
You don't really love me at all?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Just kidding.
[LAUGHING]
Cheers.
In Tagalog, it's shot puno!
- Shot puno?
- [LAUGHS]
Shot puno!
[LAUGHS]
[WHISPERS] Oh my goodness!
Drink up!
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Uh! [COUGHS]
[GIGGLING]
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Drink! Drink!
Don't look at me like that,
I can't handle it!
[HANNAH SQUEALING]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ahh!
You're the only one drinking.
Give me some.
I'll open another! You!
- Why are you--
- Shot puno!
Yes!
That's it, sir.
[GLASSES CLINK]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES SENSUAL]
It's hot!
It's really hot.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
It's hot! Whoo!
It's so hot, right?
Very hot.
Whoo!
[HANNAH BREATHING HEAVILY]
It's very hot.
Oh my gosh! Oh my gosh!
It's so hot!
Ah, sir, I'll just get
some water.
It's so hot.
- Uh.
- Hey.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]